{
    "id": "60b26980146446368f5f63f775419a7e",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………… an explanation of his conduct.",
            "description": "To call for is to demand.",
            "answers": [
                "called off",
                "called out",
                "called in",
                "called for"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… the doctor immediately.",
            "description": "To call somebody in is to summon them.",
            "answers": [
                "Call on",
                "Call in",
                "Call at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Julie ...................... us yesterday.",
            "description": "To call on somebody is to pay them a brief visit.",
            "answers": [
                "called on",
                "called in",
                "called out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandfather cannot ………………… past events.",
            "description": "To call up is to recollect.",
            "answers": [
                "call up",
                "bring out",
                "bring up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His arrogance ..................... his ruin.",
            "description": "Bring about means cause.",
            "answers": [
                "brought in",
                "brought up",
                "brought about"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The publishers are planning to ………………… a cheap edition of their new dictionary.",
            "description": "To bring out is to publish.",
            "answers": [
                "bring up",
                "bring out",
                "bring in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. the orphan as her own child.",
            "description": "To bring somebody up is to raise them.",
            "answers": [
                "brought out",
                "brought up",
                "brought in",
                "brought about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How did these things …………………..?",
            "description": "Come about means happen.",
            "answers": [
                "come up",
                "come about",
                "bring out",
                "bring about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The question ………………… before the municipal corporation last week.",
            "description": "If a question comes up, it is raised for discussion.",
            "answers": [
                "came out",
                "came up",
                "came off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He seems to be …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well out",
                "pull off",
                "run off",
                "well off"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………… against the gross injustice meted out to them.",
            "description": "To cry out is to protest loudly.",
            "answers": [
                "cried up",
                "cried out",
                "cried away"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The rope ……………….. while they were hauling up the pillar.",
            "description": "If something gives way, it breaks or snaps.",
            "answers": [
                "gave up",
                "gave in",
                "gave way",
                "gave out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}